**PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy notice for Svyatoslav Vlasov (PixelRush) ('we', 'us', or 'our"), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share ('process") your information when you use our services (Services), such as when you:

* Download and use our mobile application (1Money), or any other application of ours that links to this privacy notice
* Engage with us in other related ways, including any sales, marketing, or events

If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Services. If you still have any questions or concerns, please contact us at support@pixelrush.org.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you register on the Services, express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Services, or otherwise when you contact us. The personal information provided by You that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect may include the following:

* email addresses
* usernames
* contact or authentication data
* names
* social media login data
* financial data

Application Data. If you use our application(s), we also may collect the following information if you choose to provide us with access or permission:

* Mobile Device Data. We automatically collect device information (such as your mobile device ID, model, and manufacturer), operating system, version information and system configuration information, device and application identification numbers, browser type and version, hardware model Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, and Internet Protocol (IP) address (or proxy server). If you are using our application(s), we may also collect information about the phone network associated with your mobile device, your mobile device's operating system or platform, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device's unique device ID, and information about the features of our application(s) you accessed.
* Push Notifications. We may request to send you push notifications regarding your account or certain features of the application(s). If you wish to opt out from receiving these types of communications, vou may turn them off in vour device's settings.

This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our application(s), for troubleshooting, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use, or navigate the Services. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Services, and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes. The information we collect includes:

* Log and Usage Data. Log and usage data is service-related, diagnostic, usage, and performance information our servers automatically collect when you access or use our Services and which we record in log files. Depending on how you interact with us, this log data may include your IP address, device information, browser type, and settings and information about your activity in the Services (such as the date/time stamps associated with your usage, pages and files viewed, searches, and other actions you take such as which features you use), device event information (such as system activity, error reports (sometimes called 'crash dumps'), and hardware settings).
* Device Data. We collect device data such as information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other device you use to access the Services. Depending on the device used, this device data may include information such as your IP address (or proxy server), device and application identification numbers, location, browser type, hardware model, Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, operating system, and system configuration information.

**HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?**

We process your personal information for a variety of reasons, depending on how you interact with our Services, including:

* To facilitate account creation and authentication and otherwise manage user accounts. We may process your information so you can create and log in to your account, as well as keep your account in working order.
* To deliver and facilitate delivery of services to the user. We may process your information to provide you with the requested service.
* To respond to user inquiries/offer support to users. We may process your information to respond to your inquiries and solve any potential issues you might have with the requested service.
* To fulfil and manage your orders. We may process your information to fulfil and manage your orders, payments, returns, and exchanges made through the Services.
* To save or protect an individual's vital interest. We may process your information when necessary to save or protect an individual's vital interest, such as to prevent harm.

**WHAT LEGAL BASES DO WE RELY ON TO PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?**

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) require us to explain the valid legal bases we rely on in order to process your personal information. As such, we may rely on the following legal bases to process your personal information:

* Consent. We may process your information if vou have given us permission (i.e. consent) to use vour personal information for a specific purpose. You can withdraw your consent at any time. Learn more about withdrawing your consent.
* Performance of a Contract. We may process your personal information when we believe it is necessary to fulfil our contractual obligations to you, including providing our Services or at your request prior to entering into a contract with you.
* Legal Obligations. We may process your information where we believe it is necessary for compliance with our legal obligations, such as to cooperate with a law enforcement body or regulatory agency, exercise or defend our legal rights, or disclose your information as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.
* Vital Interests. We may process your information where we believe it is necessary to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of a third party, such as situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person.

**WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Vendors, Consultants, and Other Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your data with third-party vendors, service providers, contractors, or agents ('third parties') who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. We have contracts in place with our third parties, which are designed to help safeguard your personal information. This means that they cannot do anything with your personal information unless we have instructed them to do it. They will also not share your personal information with any organisation apart from us. They also commit to protect the data they hold on our behalf and to retain it for the period we instruct. The third parties we may share personal information with are as follows:

* Advertising, Direct Marketing, and Lead Generation: [AdMob](https://support.google.com/admob/answer/6128543?hl=en)
* Allow Users to Connect to Their Third-Party Accounts: [Google Account](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/), [Apple Account](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/)
* Functionality and Infrastructure Optimisation: [Firebase Realtime Database](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy)
* User Account Registration and Authentication: [Firebase Authentication](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy), [Google Sign-In](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/), [Apple Sign-In](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/sign-in-with-apple/)
* Web and Mobile Analytics: [Google Analytics for Firebase](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy)
* Website Performance Monitoring: [Firebase Crashlytics](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/)
* Website Testing: [Firebase Remote Config](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/)

**WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?**

The Services may link to third-party websites, online services, or mobile applications and/or contain advertisements from third parties that are not affiliated with us and which may link to other websites, services, or applications. Accordingly, we do not make any guarantee regarding any such third parties, and we will not be liable for any loss or damage caused by the use of such third-party websites, services, or applications. The inclusion of a link towards a third-party website, service, or application does not imply an endorsement by us. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of data you provide to any third parties. Any data collected by third parties is not covered by this privacy notice. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other websites, services, or applications that may be linked to or from the Services. You should review the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond to your questions.

**HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS?**

Our Services offer you the ability to register and log in using your third-party social media account details (like your Facebook or Twitter logins). Where you choose to do this, we will receive certain profile information about you from your social media provider. The profile information we receive may vary depending on the social media provider concerned, but will often include your name, email address and profile picture. We will use the information we receive only for the purposes that are described in this privacy notice or that are otherwise made clear to you on the relevant Services.

Please note that we do not control, and are not responsible for, other uses of your personal information by your third-party social media provider. We recommend that you review their privacy notice to understand how they collect, use, and share your personal information, and how you can set your privacy preferences on their sites and apps.

**HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?**

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us keeping your personal information for longer than the period of time in which users have an account with us.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymise such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?**

We have implemented appropriate and reasonable technical and organisational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, despite our safeguards and efforts to secure your information, no electronic transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorised third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Services is at your own risk. You should only access the Services within a secure environment.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

These Services do not address anyone under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 16 years of age. In the case we discover that a child under 16 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do the necessary actions.

**WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

If you would at any time like to terminate your account, you can:

* Log in to your account settings and delete your user account.
* Contact us using the contact information provided.

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, we may retain some information in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our legal terms and/or comply with applicable legal requirements.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may update this privacy notice from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. The updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible.

**HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?**

You may contact our Data Protection Officer (DPO): Svyatoslav Vlasov, by email at support@pixelrush.org, or by post at Russia, 198260, Sankt-Peterburg, ul. Soldata Korzuna 5, 244

Latest update: 2023-09-30
